crowdsourcingweek.com 2017-12-13

# Privacy Policy - Crowdsourcing Week

Ensuring the privacy and security of your personal information is very important to Crowdsourcing Week. Our Privacy Policy outlines the information we collect about you and how we use this information.

 **COOKIES**

This website or its third party tools use cookies for targeted advertising and customization purposes. This data, such as your cookies or website activity, may be used by third parties to target advertising on other sites based on your users’ online activity. To opt out of receiving targeted advertising, you can visit youronlinechoices.eu.

 **COLLECTED INFORMATION**

Your personal data is used in strict accordance with Singapore’s personal data protection laws. Processing and using your data for consultation, advertising and market research purposes only takes place with your explicit consent.

Facebook Lead Ads is a feature we make use of to provide more targeted marketing services to our users, by collecting personal information such as users’ names, email addresses, company details or other information. If you submit your data to you through our Lead Ad, your data will be governed by this Privacy Policy; No Lead Ads will be targeted to any minors. We will not re-sell any user information collected from these ads.

 **OUR EMAIL LIST**

When you sign-up to receive our emailing list, we may also collect optional information such as your name or company. We use this personal information to tailor our email messages and to enhance our service offering.

 **SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Crowdourcing Week put in place security measures for your personal data and manage your personal data in accordance with data privacy regulations in Singapore. Your personal data will only be used for the purposes for which you provided it to Crowdsourcing Week, as indicated to you at the time you provided your personal data.

 **POLICY CHANGES**

We may periodically update this Privacy Policy for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here.

 **CONTACT US**

Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Privacy Policy or the manner in which we treat your personal information or to withdraw your name from an email or other marketing list.

Please contact us using the following information: www.crowdsourcingweek.com; hello@crowdsourcingweek.com
